Guide to the International Labor Rights Forum Archive, 1986-2016 LAC0019
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Donor Files, Series 7
  - Ms. Foundation for Women, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Raphael Levy Memorial Foundation, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - Grantmakers Without Borders List, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Grassroots International, 2011 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Greater Washington Youth Philanthropy Initiative, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Greenville Foundation, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Groundspring, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Heron Foundation, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Hewlett, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Hill-Snowden Foundation, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Hitachi Foundation, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Hunt Alternative Fund, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Human and Civil Rights Organization of America, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Humanity United, 2009-2012 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - ILGWU, 2010-2011 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - International Youth Foundation, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Impact Fund, 2006-2011 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Inter America Foundation, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - International Foundation, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Levi Strauss Foundation, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Bill and Melinda Gates, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Conrad Hilton Foundation, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Donations, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Ebay Foundation, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Equal Exchange, 2011 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Eleanor Humes Hanley Fund, 2011 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Fair Food Foundation, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Free2Work, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Ford Foundation General, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Funder Calls, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Funding Exchange, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Fund for a Just Society, 2007-2008 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Fund for Nonviolence, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Fund for Southern Communities, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Gaea Foundation, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - General Service Foundation, 2008-2009 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Global Ministries, 2011 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Global Philanthropy Partnership, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - GM Foundation (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Grace Jones Richardson Trust, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- International Labor Organization Files, Series 8
  This series is arranged by subject under ILO auspices.
  - ILO Working Girls, ND (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - ILO - IPEC International Program on Elimination of Child Labor, 1996-2001 (Box 30, Folder data_value_missing_c12e9a1d7ee4385a73d7403b275a3a5d)
  - ILO Committee on MNES, 1993-1997 (Box 30, Folder data_value_missing_89c02605a1c0618e636c4c51a65522f1)
  - ILO Committee on Application of Standards, 1993 (Box 30, Folder data_value_missing_abd65d86641dc6cc8c4b871da9d2d643)
  - ILO Conference Reform, 1994 (Box 30, Folder data_value_missing_3d7aa1b1e927b4678fe93bead1bc71f9)
  - GM - ILO Lonu Papers, 1999 (Box 30, Folder data_value_missing_482c977b91af72ac704ee0dfbd8ad0e3)
  - ILO Codes of Conduct, 1991 (Box 30, Folder data_value_missing_4ed812a8019dec74aed298951d9cf30e)
  - ILO - Child Labor, 1999 (Box 30, Folder data_value_missing_1259ec10f41911aceaae30e6510fdea6)
- Campaign Research, Series 9
  This series is arranged by research subject.
  - Tobacco Industry Research, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Child Labor Memos, 2005-2010 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - China Rule of Law Program Booklet, ND (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Justice for All: a Guide to Worker Rights in the Global Economy, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Farm Bill, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Fair Labor Standards, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Drug Use and Incarceration Research, 2008-2010 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Taylor Farms/Teamsters Union Campaign, 2014-2015 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Uzbekistan Trade Data / Company Info, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Workers in the Global Economy, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Sweatshop Solutions? Economic Ground Zero in Bangladesh and Wal-Mart's Responsibility, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Firestone Agricultural Workers' Union of Liberia Surveys, ND (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous Files, Series 10
  This series is arranged by subject or organization.
  - USTR GSP Hearings, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - USTR GSP Guatemala, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - AFL-CIO GSP Petition, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - China Reports, 2003-2005 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Org #3 Quarterly Reports, 2008-2012 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - China-US Memo, 2009 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - 611 Documents, 2010 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Child Labor /Tea, 2010 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - China Grant, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Politics of Foreign Trade, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - China 570, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - GPN, 2011-2012 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Child Labor / Carpets Organizing, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - China Grants / Funding Requests, 2012-2015 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Courses, 2014 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Documents in Chinese, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - News Articles, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Kukdong/Mexico, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Kukdong/Mexico, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - GSP Anti Discrimination, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - GSP Anti Discrimination, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Robin Media List, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Price of Childhood Report, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Pineapple Research, 2006-2008 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - ILRF Literature, 2007-2008 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - General Government Files, 2008-2015 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Oak Harbor, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - GSP Submission, 2010 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Human and Civil Rights Organization of America Applications, 2010-2011 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Various Campaign Files- Cocoa, 2010-2014 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Trade Labor GSP Avenues, ND (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Forced Labor Research, ND (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Forced Labor Research, ND (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Honduras GSP USTR Correspondence, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - USTR Reports, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - AFL-CIO GSP Petitions, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Thai Economy, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - White House on HR, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Mexico Maquiladoras, 1991-1998 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence and Notes, 1994-1999 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Thailand Politics, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - White House Code of Conduct, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - CBI Parity Bill, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Seasonal Labor Research, 1995-1999 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - AFL-CIO WTO Task Force, 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Workers Rights Caucus WTO, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Unsitragua Guatemala, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - White House Trade Policy, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - University of Michigan Conference on Trade, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - AFL-CIO GSP Petitions, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Honduras PVH, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - National Consumers League, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Various Campaign Files- Child Labor, 1999-2007 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1999-2007 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Awards Information, 1999-2016 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Sexual Harassment in the Workplace Research, 2001-2003 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Sexual Harassment in the Workplace Research, 2006-2007 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous research, 2000-2002 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Health and Safety in the Workplace Reports, 2000-2010 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Labor Rights Monitoring, 2010 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - USLEAP Reports, 2013 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Brochures, 1983-1999 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - GSP Contents, 1984-1988 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - USTR Hearing and Testimony, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Labor Rights and GSP Press Packet, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - GSP Regulations, 1985-1988 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Labor Code, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Thailand GSP, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Pacific Islands Research, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Federal Regulations and Notions, 1987-1990 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - GSP Subcommittee Petition, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Inter-Agency Committee GSP, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Petition for GSP Subcommittee, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Forced Labor Research, 1987-1994 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - GSP Testimony, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Audiovisual content, Series 11
  This series is arranged by program title.
  - The Dark Side of Chocolate Documentary, 2010 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - The Battle of the Invisibles DVD, ND (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - ISF Documentary on Communism, KMU, and the NPA by Child Herbolingo (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Pilipinismo Welga DVD, ND (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - ISF Documentary "Welga", ND (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Real Sports #138 DVD, ND (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Entrevistas Fotos (IRLF) DVD, ND (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Pictures and Videos DVD (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Kenya Photos DVD, ND (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - ILRF Note Cards Revised, ND (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - India: Bihar, Orissa, Uttar Pradesh, and West Bengal "In The Interests of Children" Photos, 2001 (Box 37, Dvd 1)
  - India: Bihar, Orissa, Uttar Pradesh, and West Bengal "In The Interests of Children" Photos, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Indonesia: Bekasi, Jermals (Sumatra), and Jakarta "In the Best Interests of Children" Photos, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Indonesia: Bekasi, Jermals (Sumatra), and Jakarta "In the Best Interests of Children" Photos, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - "Murder" Liz/ILRF DVD, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - International Labor Rights Forum Annual Report DVD, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - International Labor Rights Forum Annual Report DVD, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - International Labor Rights Forum Annual Report DVD, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Stolen Childhoods Documentary, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Wal-Mart Hub DVD, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Sa Ngalan Ng Tubo Documentary, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Olga Tutillo + Ricardo Zamideo Speaking in the US Flower Events DVD, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Against All Odds Documentary, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Youth Activists Against Child Labor Asalute Documentary, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Rollback Wal-Mart: Video of the Conference and Quarantine Wal-Mart Demo Kansas City, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Wal-Mart Workers Tour Bangor, Maine DVD, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - ILRF Notecards for Ted Coyle DVD, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Wal-Mart DVD, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - MHSSN Factory Photos China, Indonesia, and Guatemala, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - House of Justice Documentary, 2009 (Box 37, Folder 20)